all right welcome to fix the world
Friday
I still like saying it makes you feel
feel happy and a little a little echoic
yeah yeah welcome it's our live board
meeting for creating idea cafe and which
is our first project and together Tec
the global tech cooperative that is
going to meet all of our needs with
technology starting with a way to
communicate with idea cafe so as we're
talking before went live I participated
slash hosted for idea cafes this week on
communism and Marxism because that was a
somewhat divisive topic and the group
were both part of and people were
seeking like getting their feathers
ruffled over miscommunication of
definitions and and how much is Marxism
ideals and values could be part of a
game be and some people think not at all
can't be other people were like well
there's some good stuff here and so I
set up what was going to be one idea
cafe and then Jordan hall suggested
people sign up for them so then a lot of
people signed up for them and it ended
up being one very popular one which I
then Slyke shifted people around and got
it ended up that it was just three of us
at each of them which is kind of the
perfect number for an idea cafe three or
four five is a little too many for a
half an hour conversation two is great I
mean it's a conversation but it's not
really an idea cafe and three is
everyone has up to five minutes to talk
that's 15 minutes maximum and then 15
minutes of dialogue after so I it was
interesting because I learned a lot I
mean it wasn't divisive it wasn't
divisive at all it was like well I don't
know whether it was the group of people
that they were game be people who were
practicing the Omega rule or whether it
was the topic it just so happened that
most of the people were exactly what I
was saying they were like there's some
beauty there's some good stuff here and
there's a lot of bad stuff under
communism Marxism and we want the good
and not the bad and that's of course my
interpretation of what they said but
there was no division in that there was
no yes it
100% right we should be trying to
instill it nor was it 100% wrong there's
nothing of value there it was
interesting because because of this
format I had suggested we record it like
I do with all the idea cafes on the
channel and then afterwards we would
stop recording and we would vote on
whether or not to make it public and
everyone voted to make it public but the
fact that they could vote to delete it
and they could vote to keep it private
meant that they were more comfortable
speaking their mind and then after the
fact the fact that everyone voted to
make it public was interesting because I
think that that that gives it a
different dynamic then it automatically
been recorded and published or not being
recorded at all right like it's a
different it also though even under that
we kind of generally ended up having a
bit of a conversation after we stopped
recording and it's still a different
energy and a different dynamic when
you're not recording at all then like
where they know it's not gonna be on
YouTube and that's the difference
between the idea cafe that we're
creating the platform and the YouTube
channel is there isn't kind of an option
for it to be on the YouTube channel and
not have people watch it unless it stays
private but then it's not really on the
YouTube channel versus the platform were
creating where it can be you have access
to yours and the people who participated
have access to it but not the general
public how about access to it and then
people voting and say yes we want people
to have general access to it so that was
just a really good learning and I felt
after the fourth one like I kind of want
to pick a more divisive topic like I
want to have like a real one with like I
don't say like everyday people but like
random people that are like this is a
divisive topic like what do you think
about Trump from Trump supporters and
not and like see see how that works just
because I wanted to kind of see how
conflict works in a video type format
because the questions designed for it
not necessarily to be divisive but quite
frankly how do you feel / think about
Marxism communism isn't an undivided
question it's not really like designed
in a way to not be confrontational but
it's also not do you agree
with Marxism communism right which is
like then we're kind of starting off on
a debate instead of right yeah you can
give your thoughts and I can give my
thoughts and they don't have to match up
but they did you know they did tend to
find the connections the truth truth
amongst it so I just want to update you
on that I don't want to take too long
talking about that because we have a
agenda or going through but I just
wanted to let you know I do think that
maybe you might want to participate in
an idea cafe at some point so maybe we
can brainstorm what topic you'd really
like to discuss that's a big piece of it
is if it's something you don't want to
talk about it's not gonna be as
interesting as yeah I wish I could have
made one of those I was just wasn't able
to but they sounded interesting do you
know there seem to have been at least
one person that was very that was seem
to be very emotional about the topic do
you know if that was if that person
participated the other people you happen
to know she did not did she develop a
she was kind of and so but we're
actually looking at doing one together
next week I kind of offered her any
gauge she didn't want to talk about
communism Marx says because it is a
hot-button issue for her and so finding
one that she does want to talk about and
that's good yeah sorry continually I was
just when I posted the four the four
idea cafes in the game B space and
Facebook and I also suggested that I
would like to have a weekly game B idea
cafe that is just to like explore those
issues I think that's the most powerful
conversations to kind of see what idea
cafe can be right that is people who
want to help create a better world
facilitating conversations and then
figuring out what that platform looks
like to facilitate those conversations
and they're just conversations I want to
be a part of and so if you also want to
be a part of those conversations maybe
we can pick another time that isn't 11
a.m. on Friday right that works for both
of us and you don't have to make
everyone right but if you're making
one every couple weeks and then other
people know to keep coming to that one I
don't know if that appeals to you but we
can always it'd be good to yeah it'd be
good to experience it from the inside I
think that also provides a lot of
insight like you said you thought you
learned a lot from it
so yeah yeah do you want to do we this
first time using the agenda we have we
have a strip's by a few things do you
want to just go by the ones with the
most asterisks there were two yeah I
just I mean you added someone that I
think Gutter of you added your own
Asterix I did and then I added an
Asterix to one of yours and so yeah we
have two with asterisks and let's see
what else we got through I think sure
yeah so the first one I'd put on there
discuss where the goals benefits and
values of ideas cafe and the reason that
that came up and I'm thinking now it may
be premature for this but was that I was
kind of writing down some of the kind of
feature ideas we had and I was realizing
that the way those features are written
and implemented will have a lot to do
with what we want the result to be so I
want to see if you've thought about that
yet and the other option could be you
know we're too early let's just
experiment with it and let something
grow out of it so yeah I think it's a
little bit of both I don't know can you
see people's comments when they ask
questions on here could you see it on
the side the comment Jacob had just
asked I think it I don't know if we need
to talk about it now because we're doing
with the agenda but I think that's a
good question of how do you come up with
or decide on the topics would you accept
questions from the audience watching and
yes absolutely not aside from this
because we're doing kind of a board
meeting an agenda from the idea cafe
absolutely that's kind of part of it is
asking what people want to talk about on
the YouTube channel and then talking
about it and engaging and eventually on
the platform that is what I have kind of
written down here for more of the user
story of if you want people to be able
to participate in a way that they want
that yeah submitting a question and and
honing a question so it's less divisive
and just something that people want to
talk about and that's I don't want to
have to come up with every question yes
I would love people to submit questions
I'd be able to
both and that's why we're playing with
the tools like for the agenda of how do
we upload even agenda items that we're
going to be talking about yeah maybe we
maybe just you so I proposed a couple
tools there's a meeting meeting pulse
where people can anonymously put things
in and vote things up which you know
would have its disadvantages but that's
one option to use that just for idea
cafe as well and that that would be a
quick link that you can just throw
everywhere and people can that's where
there's enough context yeah then they
can just put ideas in and people can
vote them up especially for the game be
idea cafe if we want it to be weekly
both the time period the time and the
question itself let's yeah it's thinking
for the time period there's also doodle
doodle comm allows people to put in
their kind of calendar and availability
and find the most available time so
that's that's one of the options out
there I don't know if it's easier to do
that or to just like set out a couple
times and who can attend is who can the
first like it was super popular it was
too popular right once Jordan was like
yeah people should attend this I was
like no fifteen people's too many five
is the maximum like there was going to
be one with five and I would have been
the sixth person and I was just gonna
host it and hope one person kind of
didn't show up which and then many of
them didn't show up but it was just the
three of us so that's part of I guess my
own internal struggle is like how do you
put something out there and then also
limit it like also be like the first
three or the three that just where my
need for infinity has to be honed in of
like do I have the same people again and
again because that can be its own mm-hmm
beautiful thing or you didn't get a
participate before so someone who hasn't
participated gets priority right and I
think there's both first room for both
and opening it up to have more more idea
cafes like yeah so we we definitely need
to figure out that scheduling thing that
seems like one of the main features that
is not well I don't know like you said
it could it could
affect a lot of what the final
experience is based on that because is
it is it always trying to get new people
is it always trying to ask the same
question in multiple groups like we
talked about you know if we want these
ideas to build on each other that it
almost be useful although it can happen
if we're posting videos on on some if
we're posting the videos then people can
build on that on the next meeting if you
if you want to have that topic happen
multiple times but it comes down to are
we are we trying to build up a knowledge
and get a consensus among a community or
are we just creating a space for people
to communicate on challenging ideas okay
so do you have a preference okay but
which really means the first one right
to be able to and that's where with the
with I don't remember the exact question
you asked on the agenda but that discuss
the goals benefits and values for the
idea cafe and I wrote like to me values
that I don't even think this is Vanessa
you're talking I think you're talking
more like the value that the customer /
user gets right like what is it would
have been DM and I was kind of answering
it in terms of like value driven right
like bringing love in bringing passion
like values and I was like I don't know
if this is the same question but at any
rate I said diversity in connection and
I think both of those things are for
both like those are the values that I
want it to instill is the diversity of
like you don't need to agree with me to
attend right we need to be able to have
a diversity of ways of communicating a
diversity of I don't and build into the
system to to maybe not in the beta but
build into the system how to keep
diversity and safety right like how do
we make sure everyone can use it if they
want to and yet at the same time people
who don't want to be at the same table
which already happens in the idea cafe
last week how do I get them separate
right and then moving people around and
that was part of usually utilizing the
tools for both scheduling and
coordinating like there was the one
where five people were going to attend
and two people showed up because
contacting people on Facebook in a group
message and I'm not friends with them
they don't necessarily
get it they don't necessarily know plans
change there's no way to communicate
back and so even having I mean I don't
want to say the people who didn't show
up get it like a mark against them or
something but at the same time to see
okay well if you say you're gonna show
up repeatedly and you don't show up
there's a problem there especially if
you're taking a time spell oh like a
space spot that somebody else would have
used right it's different when there's
thousands of people having a
conversation and a table went from
having four people to three people not a
problem but when it's the YouTube
channel and there's only so many space
for people to be able to participate
that's a it's different yeah yeah if
there's enough people then it could just
be who's ever available and it would
limit it to four people but we're gonna
have to have scheduling mm-hmm I mean
even when it reaches that mass the
scheduling would still be helpful like
if you know you're gonna be available at
a certain time yeah
and I'm down like this one was a little
too much doing the four doing it on
something I thought was going to be
divisive just yesterday I had two of
them which is maybe what made me a
little more exhausted but having three
maybe even like an hour apart on one day
which works a little better from even if
by the end if I'm hosting instead of
participating I think that's also
different I don't need to have my brain
on as much like I could participate and
then host another two and have them on
one day and have it be the same question
if there's multiple people who want to
participate in that game b-type
conversation right if we have an amazing
question it starts with like this one's
available I don't know just playing off
of like what could could be within my
capacity I know the tool to to build it
to grow it yeah so let me think through
this so the we know the scheduling is a
big feature mm-hmm the feature we
discussed so if the - if what we want to
get out of this is is is a kind of a
one-time experience that people will
hopefully grow from then we don't need
to repeat the questions
yeah so I'm just kind of analyzing what
our initial goal is and then we can
build upon it but it sounds like we
don't need to have to roll anything into
the design immediately that that is
trying to you know do what we talked
about before where you're we're pulling
information out of those meetings and in
building upon that it's really just if
we can have people talk and safely about
interesting or challenging discussions
then that's a win mm-hmm
yeah no absolutely because also I think
eventually I kind of have written down
here somewhere
part of we had top of this last week
part of creating the idea cafe is to use
the idea cafe to create all of together
text projects and so a piece of that is
once we have the beta once we have
something that's very easy to use even
if the beta it's just the YouTube
channel and and zoom that the community
the crowd can help us build that right
and say what works for them is the
Google Doc work does you know what I
mean like what what do we need to be
able to for you to understand the
information that came before what do you
need to sit here and have built on the
last questions
nothing you just want to attend and be
part of it or do you want kind of you
know like a broken down version of what
we're we've you've come to so far my
guess is both there's gonna be people
who want to just show up and have a
conversation and people who wanted to
both and they might be in opposition
right you might not want to sit at a
table with people who don't understand
what's going on
and so there might need to be that how
do we um orchestrate you know those kind
of those kind of issues but I like to
solve problems before they occur and
that's not necessarily the best the best
thing right like if yeah that's because
there's both infinite possibility and
also yeah like until there's someone who
says this is the kind of tool and that
one that you guys already decided on
doesn't work for me we work with what we
got yeah so I'm thinking though if we
want to get people interested in
building idea cafe what we tell them
we're building from the beginning is the
thing that people will be attracted to
or not attracted to so that will kind of
bias the people
being involved so if we say it's it's a
it's an experience
it's the singular experience that you
can repeat and then that would attract
certain people and have people focus on
a certain thing if we say it's a mass
agreement tool right to build agreement
or to fight our divisive 'no sin our
society then that would kind of attract
a separate group of people on the design
but if we don't have anything if we say
this is just a thing if we're not
specific about that I don't think it'd
attract anybody because people won't
have a place in their mind to put it
mm-hmm so I'm struggling with how to
describe it in a way that's attractive
but isn't pigeonhole it yeah and I think
that that is something that I struggle
with personally as an individual is like
creating the elevator pitch creating the
the thing of like this is what it is and
so I can brainstorm about it we can kind
of keep figuring out what what that is
and it doesn't need to be like it can
change back and forth from week to week
until we kind of get to a yes this is it
right and until it does resonate and we
do have a group of people then kind of
almost create it together I have here
that what I see it being is very much
this individual piece and the group
piece that for the individual it's about
being heard and connecting right it's
the experience like you said and for the
group it's about having an effective
conversation that is moved forward that
moves your product you know like that
and those things are very intertwined
that of course if you don't have
individuals you don't have a group but
also if it's not enjoyable for the
individual they're not going to show up
again to be part of the group and if the
group becomes dominant it's all about
the group and all about it being
effective then it's gonna be pushing
people out who aren't having an
enjoyable experience right if they're
just there to be seen it heard and
they're not part of creating an
effective you know project together and
so there's something about it of like
it's showing up and having it for the
individual with the understanding that
underlining that is when groups
naturally form we want to be able to
support that and be able to like
learn how to guide that process for the
group right like the same as for the
individual like how do we make it
enjoyable and effective for you as an
individual to participate in and grow as
a human being awesome that's all we ever
accomplish that's huge
and then when groups naturally form how
do we have that same thing exist for
groups does that make some amount of
sense yeah so building on that I think
though if if you're gonna have a group
this type of tool seems to only be
needed in a group with over like 10
people over 12 right so it's when you
have a large group of people that are
interested in a goal having them work
together where they're not all in the
same meeting you know they don't have to
all yeah where everyone has a chance to
speak yeah and that's the weird part
about it being a YouTube channel is
they're actually very different things
right the conversation itself is
important and about the individual and
then the group piece is how do you all
have an effective individual piece and
have that come together and the platform
we're creating I believe focuses on the
second one because we can do the first
one just on the YouTube channel like you
can have just a conversation on
everything it's the coordination of
those conversations that the platform
will do so no it does both there was
something other piece there that was
underlining
I remember I'm sure it'll come back so
what I'm thinking
with our talking is that's kind of a
mass brainstorming tool like you know so
like large groups can explore a goal or
a thought space or something like that
together without having to be all
together at the same time and because
the conversation doesn't get effective
above isn't effective above for people
it's that's direct communication like
YouTube or television or something when
you get above a certain number of people
it's not a conversation but this is a
way to have a lot conversation among a
large group of people
that is individual right like because
I'm in Twitter he's having a
conversation with a large group of
people but it's not effective it's like
having that interpersonal I feel like I
contributed I feel like I was heard and
having that move the group forward still
and that's what the World Cafe does that
were kind of trying to mimic and I guess
that was my it keeps almost being there
and then going away like the
individualizing entry human
communication by ernesto yep yep
applying human bandwidth by improving
listening and caring maximizing a true
human communication sounds good there
you go yeah I don't have access to add
to pop them on the screen do i no no
unfortunately I'm sure stream yards
pretty new but I'm sure eventually I'll
be able to make someone like an
admittance yeah yeah exactly
City been paid yet they gave me like a
free version I'm like I don't want the
free like it's a weird I'm like that's
bad marketing like wait til I need the
free version then give me a version or
sorry the professional version they give
me right time to experience they're like
here's the free version for a week that
doesn't help me I'm using the free one
sorry yeah I also copy these into our
notes unless you already have them I
would like I think those are excellent
concepts I would like something that
uses language that's a little bit more
Universal and that's like something
people who are on Twitter understand
like meaning that um like I don't even
know what Twitter's is but like
Twitter's mission right of like that you
understand you just put out a blurb and
a bunch of people see it like to have
something simple enough that anyone can
kind of be like yes I want to be a part
of that I want to try it I want to I
want to experience it and that's thing
is
oh that's what I was trying to sow part
of having an effective conversation with
the larger group is like beyond just
scheduling is making sure there's a
threshold of scheduling right that
doesn't quite you want to have three
people to some minimum but you really
want three people because one person's
maybe not going to show up and then you
have two people like three to five
people per timeslot on the platform on
YouTube that's what I want per timeslot
to be an effective an effective host
once we have that we can use zoom to
kind of really branch out and have then
we want more than three then we want a
minimum of twelve people per time so we
can actually have a cafe like where
you're breaking off into groups and then
coming back in and breaking off into
groups and you have them you know half
an hour but you're randomly put into a
three to five person group right to have
to have a conversation for half an hour
and then brought back in and then either
there's a whole new group of people for
the next time slot or you can continue
to be part of it and experience it again
although when you're brought back
together as a main group in those cafes
is there is there actual
because what I guess what I'm thinking
is that we have the benefit of not
having everyone in one physical location
so it could be a grouping those
groupings can happen at any time but
what's what's when the group comes
together so you have like you know 50
people in a room after the things is
there any value that we need to
replicate in the system that happens as
a group or is that just disseminating
like if they're reading off their sheets
of paper of the things that they did and
the whole group's hearing that then
maybe that's the whole group watching
the summary video at the end of someone
summarizing what they learned or
something rather than having it all have
to be scheduled at the same time yeah it
doesn't necessarily need to be scheduled
at the same time it's more if there's
only four people available no problem
we're hosted on YouTube and we're
growing it we're playing with it and
find you know how it works and what
doesn't work
once there's more people for a specific
time slot then we go to zoom and do it
so I guess what I'm it's more a tool to
find out where we are
with the lit minimal amount of my labour
human labour right to be like it took a
lot of work to organize the idea cafe
isn't be like who's available when and
who's sitting with whom and who's doing
to be able to say okay well when are you
available and how do we get you to an
idea cafe as a user and how do we make
them so that there's the table of three
to five people and when there are
multiple people who want to be part of
that time slot how do we effectively
break you into groups and that's using
zoom and not YouTube channel right and
so I don't know because I'm not I don't
know how to what the beta it looks like
at all of like what that bridge is right
like what that is the platform right is
to get individuals just kind of submit
their schedule to say what when they're
gonna be available and then have them
show actually show up right because if I
say I'm available Monday to Friday 9:00
to 4:00 I'm not really available Monday
to Friday 9:00 to 4:00 I want two slots
during that time period and I want a
week's advance notice or I wanted
24-hour advance notice um and then
making sure if it does that make sense
like it's so although I have my schedule
when I'm free I don't want to be
scheduled for that entire amount of time
I want to know who I'm talking to and
then be matched up and then yes it can
happen all throughout the week and it
doesn't need to be everyone's talking
all at the same time yeah I'm just gonna
put them on here so I can read them like
random one slot minutes for the
participants to ensure everyone is
listening and paying attention sorry
honest I don't know what that means
I think it's talking about a larger
group and tell me if my audio is really
bad but well you can have an audience of
fifty people but these five minute slots
maybe that one person being shown to all
50 people oh that's what yeah no no and
then he said so everyone knows that
you're being that they're listening and
paying attention so it's not like that
would kind of make sense in what we're
doing right now if we really cared that
there was an audience of twenty people
and we care if they were listening to
paying attention that's not really a
problem an idea Cafe because you're it's
like sitting around a coffee table
having a conversation you can see that
the people are paying attention or not
cuz you're talking to them and there was
like one of them where I was trying to
find this because there was echo
and so I was off-screen while I was
searching around for it and I was still
listening but I had to verbally say that
right like it's a different it's as in
person as you can get well it's also
part of it and if there's someone who's
not painted who's like you know not
being like interrupting everyone not
paying attention doing everything but
paying attention they're not gonna be
invited you're not gonna want to sit
with them again and if there's a way to
actually say those things like I don't
want to be matched with this person
again
yeah that part of the attack that might
not be beta and Jubilee the the plan so
the way you did those four is that each
person had five minutes to talk and then
you had fifty 15 minutes of pretty much
unstructured discussion time yeah okay
so it is important that everyone's
present at the same time so that you can
have that structured time after they've
fully listened to the other participants
right that's an important important part
oh yes no the three to five people being
available at the same time for the
entire conversation that is key that is
an idea cafe that ours happens at 1 p.m.
and someone else has happens at 3 p.m.
that doesn't necessarily matter but it
very much matters we were present during
the same time otherwise it's a
completely different platform right if
I'm just putting out my 5 minutes of
what I think about Marxism communism and
then other people are listening to that
and responding that could be a platform
but it's not a conversation right then
I'm looking at you like I look at anyone
on YouTube and I'm like judging you and
I'm gonna make this point at this point
right like we're not connecting we're
not having an actual conversation yeah
I'm responding to a video let me throw
an idea out that made me horrible a
brainstorm is what if we recorded the 5
minutes beforehand and then part of the
process is you could watch that
beforehand and then you're scheduled for
the time to talk together I don't know
if that's better or worse it would it
might make the schedule a little easier
but it also I don't know I think I like
it both ways because I think that one
we're not using a half an hour but then
also you're using 15 minutes like if
we're if I know I'm scheduled with you
and three other people I'm kind of have
homework
I've listening to those before I should
up and talked there's a beauty there
that I'm recording mine first so I'm not
basing them on what you said right so
I'm giving you my full unfiltered
version of my question unpin it which is
just not quite a conversation but it has
power in and of itself the issue is then
are people actually gonna sit there and
listen to them right or we're gonna have
different and so and the other question
is so then I'm scheduled to talk to
three other people and I sit and listen
through 15 minutes of listening and then
two of them don't show up and I now have
two other random people right it's like
that's part of it it's like oh wait I
listen to the different homework now
I've got to listen to these people talk
so I don't know if it would be effective
with an idea cafe but it's possibly an
iteration down the line of like what
people might want write it to be like
right and the more because you could
watch a ton of them be like I want to
talk to these people I would actually
sit you at a table with people that you
like want to have a conversation with
right and someone who has let's say
Jordan Hall in the game v-space has tons
of people who want to talk to him either
he has his pick of who he wants to talk
to or it's randomized for you know what
I mean he's he's picked his people and
because they've picked him he kind of
has his pick right and the rest of us
are like yes I want to talk to these
people in it and it matches us up based
on I didn't hate you you know you were
we were okay with each other like you're
up voting and down voting right there
were there weren't enough people present
who you up voted so instead you didn't
down vote them right like I don't know
those kind yeah something like that we'd
have to work out all those different
yeah things so I see it's moving forward
what we need to accomplish is for the
next steps is to figuring out just the
feature set for the scheduling that we
need because everything else I was
trying to build out too far in the
future which is like we said that's one
of my biases is always trying to design
way far down we don't have people
participating and then like you said we
need to really kind of figure out the
pitch the pitch has to be broad enough
that that it doesn't pigeonhole anyone
into what this is going to look like
which is my big problem
then but it needs to be specific enough
that people are interested in it because
if it's like oh we're just solving the
world's problems everyone's gonna be
like well I'd you know I'm not gonna
find time for that mm-hmm and I yeah and
that's the question is do we want to
draw in the people who want to solve the
world's problems I kind of do I hate
like I thought it's kind of and that
sort with the user stories I was kind of
after having looked through like the
inmates running the asylum I was drawn
to this book which is kind of a bad name
but it's called why high tech products
drive us crazy and how to restore the
sanity and it talks about of course the
user user experience and picking someone
who's like somewhat a real person and
and building it for them and sitting
with that I was like we're the real
people were building it for right like
right now it's you and I and so yes I
know we kind of need to think about like
mythical people that will come on board
but also we kind of don't that like what
we want is I want to help the world you
want to help the world what what areas
do we want to help it we both want to
help it in tech it sounds like but what
other areas right and then building it
potentially for two to three like food
or I don't know I don't know if that
appeals but having the people themselves
saying what they want to work on instead
of thinking what other people want to
work on and making a user profile that's
the beauty of creating a cooperative and
having people involved and having to be
transparent is we somewhat don't need to
make up mythical people we get real
people and ask them does this meet your
needs how is this for you
what would make it better so I also had
a thought that it'd be good to get some
sort of scheduling system but if there
isn't if there isn't something that
already exists that we can't kind of
like hack together to make something
that works and there might be but
another option is to hire a virtual
assistant and just have a real person
kind of handle that scheduling stuff
temporarily and see how it works that
would have a cost of course but yeah you
know even working on systems has a cost
of time right yeah absolutely and and
that's also although we're not in silly
there yet if we grow this and there's
people watching it there can be someone
who's like listen I have four hours to
dedicate to that a week right it doesn't
necessarily need to be a paid position
someone who's not comfortable being on
camera but is comfortable to be no
scheduling piece there's a piece of it I
like but I don't like all of it like I'm
like I kind of liked figure you know
like okay this person's available at
this point and spreadsheet in it I'd
like a piece of paper and doing that but
I can't do that without the rest of it
so it doesn't really work and just how
do we communicate with people Facebook's
not a great way and that's yes so so the
action items that I'm building it's like
figure out if we could build a
scheduling
well maybe list out the requirements for
a scheduling system bill see what tools
are out there to build it like you know
how can doodle be used how can other
things views and then just kind of
brainstorm on on the elevator pitch yeah
I think those are three things that I'm
seeing that that we could probably work
on yeah we might not get through those
today we might be sitting with them for
the agenda next week also I don't know
if you saw just on the agenda
I had hyperlinks to these so after we've
talked about it I made it like each date
you can go back and watch it if you want
to so that anyone else going forward
they come and be the third person if
they wanted to they could go back and
watch them right and if not they have
the UM what we talked about and find out
what we what we decided the glass we can
we decided the idea cafes what word is
our first project and so all along we
didn't talk about maybe we should make a
separate section just for potential
discussions me aside from agenda like
meeting well I'm missing like agenda I
don't we're not going to get through a
ton of this mm-hm
we have some things on there that I
suggested that we're probably not going
to I think we just copy like anything we
didn't finish and
and shiny but we just mention a tweet
right and yeah is what I thought how I
thought it was going to go I don't know
me but there's some that's a good idea
tech stuff but or if there doesn't need
to necessarily be in there
my edition did not even think made sense
no it's like rule Omega and quirks I was
just that was more dealing with the
individual person that there's yeah
anyway I don't even know we'll discuss
that in a future date of like how you
deal with people who like it in person
this is kind what I'm talking about
in person if we're talking I would tell
you I'm deaf in one ear so that you know
not talk to be on that side I'm not
ignoring you there's other things that
happen online and it can be like listen
I clear my throat so in rolls their eyes
it's not acting like and so I did having
that as a piece of communication so that
you know this doesn't mean what it
usually means in human language right
and happy not be a piece of it is an
important piece for me as someone with a
disability to say hey I have autism I'm
gonna come off a little different I have
a TD I'm gonna come off a little
different and that's not I don't want
you to gauge it based on based on that
and I do think that at some point we
need to talk about that but I didn't
know how to write that out and to put it
in the agenda besides what I put which I
think personal quirks Omega which I'm
trying to abide by more and more just in
everyday life yeah maybe just to start
if people have any things that they
think that they're aware of that other
people on the first time meeting on my
you know to mention that you have any
effect ations or anything that yeah and
that's a part of it though is like that
your pronouns like there's certain
things that although I'm comfortable
sharing that I'm deaf with you 30
seconds into meeting you most people
aren't and having almost like a business
card as part of your profile of like hey
these are the people you're talking to
so you're not using time every time
you're like one because then you can
mismatch with people that aren't part of
the quirks right like if me clearing my
throat is gonna really annoy someone we
probably shouldn't be matched up
together if someone has you know ticks
and Tourette's and and like making sure
that not only do you not want to take
the time every time to explain that and
the vulnerability every time to explain
that but it also means whether or not
we're compatible or not right to have it
to have a conversation because none of
those things make us go to bad people
right like I clear my throat or that you
get annoyed by it isn't it's only
relevant that we don't want it to
detract from the conversation and so to
have that be a piece of like user
profiles again we might not be able to
match people in the beta based on that
but later on with more money more
project power more you know people who
know how to code those kind of things we
have more and more ways of doing that
and honor you know that it was that's
part of the diversity of values the
values and diversity is like how do you
match people up without making anyone
wrong so that they can connect further
right so they're not sitting there with
those triggers that don't need to be
there sorry I come to kind of detracted
us what we were actually talking about
no I think I got I just wanted to write
down those extra times while they're on
top of my head so yeah so I so yeah I'm
not sure where were you is there
anything that's coming to mind that
you'd like to any of these actions you'd
like to hit next holding holding them
all in my head doesn't quite work but
did you write them on the agenda are
they on there oh no there's an action
item section underneath the ARS yes
gotcha Yeah right out schedule the
requirements business card profile look
for tech to use to build the scheduler I
mean that's awesome
looking for tech we're not gonna do
right now right that's more oh these are
actions for after they'd like for us to
take on I'm not bad otherwise I would
know I'd already know what the a what it
was for looking for tech to use for the
scheduler brainstorm elevator pitch that
one I can sit with and writing and try
to do and even crowdsource it on my
Facebook page of like hey that's what
happened I was meeting with someone on
Friday mornings he's a politician here I
don't remember one second I'm just gonna
go grab it for my mirror cuz I can't
read it this far and we actually had an
elevator pitch for the
one second it took me all day to write
it that he liked home I was like that's
much better it was mission where people
come for meaningful conversations and
generate solutions together I don't know
if that actually works now for what
we're doing that was before it was ever
a YouTube channel that was just when it
was no I like that I like that it's it
it hits the main point and as the
secondary in there mm-hmm so yeah do you
mind
I wanna noodle over it I love how cuz I
was I was literally just going to be
like we've we thought we had an elevator
pitch for something that somebody help
me home and I'm like it's literally for
this for this that it was try to find
out where it is action item look for
tech to use right out scheduler you did
you delete the thing I was ready to
Center why is this not working I don't
think so
action item Omega okay it's not letting
me do because I'm trying to be you I
think is the issue okay she's like
you're a little red thing anyway oh is
it called the mission elevator pitch
wishing elevator pitch they're slightly
different but
ever would I do without spellcheck type
you need spellcheck even me still
celebrate misstatement where people come
for meaningful conversation and generate
solutions together I mean that doesn't
include the piece of it being around a
question but I don't know if it needs to
be that I think that was where he had
helped me hone it because I had that all
kind of in there and then it was like
right they get that right you don't need
to put on Twitter that it's like their
mission statement doesn't include in 250
characters like it's like okay yeah it's
yeah yeah I think it's understood that
the only topic based and you can even so
that would be like the full mission
statement but just a tagline or slogan
it'll be something like meaningful
conversations that generate solutions or
I'm wondering meaningful is useful but
one of the interesting things about this
is that so I don't know if word like
intimate might even work because we're
taking the extra energy to put everyone
on video together at the same time so
that's where people come for intimate
conversations and generate solutions
together or just where people come for
intimate conversations is kind of what
we're that is kind of what I do at cafe
that YouTube channel is mmhmm right
because we're not generating solutions
together it's like how do you guys all
help me deal with my like my need for
conversation and to create this platform
it's kind of what without saying that's
what it is like it's what conversations
do I want to be a part of and host and
I'm totally open to whatever
conversations other people want to be a
part of but I've never hosting one on
sports like it's just not right so maybe
I want to do is somebody else like once
we have the platform and someone else
wants to show up I would never tell
anyone else they can't have that
conversation but yes and that's good I
think I'll think more about that in the
coming weekend all right maybe we can
have a couple ideas to review for next
all right and the schedule requirements
I can also kind of sit and brainstorm as
far as like I don't necessarily know the
language around it but I have sat with
like this is what as an individual I
want it to do right like this is what I
want my dashboard to kind of have
like I want to be able to say my
schedule and have it match me with
people and tell me how does it tell me
right it needs to have an alert that
says yes you're talking at 2:00 p.m. on
Tuesday two people confirm needs to have
that confirmation piece so that yes oh
turns out no I was available all week
and then things got nope not available
yeah I would be perfect so yeah
yeah any any any requirements that you
can think of all right sounds good do
you want to I know it wasn't really on
the agenda today but I think those are
kind of the action items as far as we
could talk through that more here or we
could um the spreadsheet for tech that
exists to have the the columns I know we
didn't asterisk next to those ones but
it used to had said you had some ideas
of what I just kind of threw up what
what works because I keep coming into
contact with new tech and then I want to
put it somewhere so I don't have to
constantly keep them straight or have
them be told about again and again and I
think it helps if and when one of the
projects is the app for ideas too or
sorry the app for tech Yelp for apps be
able to say these ones are what already
exists this is already within that that
realm of and I liked your idea of not
having the tabs along the bottom and
have you notes own column of like that
yeah Kory a category of what it what it
solves yeah so I was also wondering I
was thinking through this like some of
them are tools that we just would use to
get to game B but they wouldn't they're
not necessarily a tool designed some of
them we would be using because we don't
have time to build a whole tool but
they're very kind of anti game be like
to have a discussion on you know and and
maybe there's some stuff out there that
it's like this was game B before we knew
a game he was right so it'd be nice to
have some something that says like how
game B ish it is or of course we
probably don't know enough about game B
to do that yet yeah but something that
had some of the values a game be like
you know is it for profit
and all the stuff is it I think without
it necessarily saying game be checkmark
not checkmark or you know score out of
10 who oh that's where I was kind of
like I'm like I don't even know how to
tell who owns it but like is it owns
right is it owned on the stock market is
it owned by ten people is it owned is it
like Wikipedia is a not-for-profit but
it's still owned by specific group of
people right it's not owned by humanity
but nothing is owned by humanity that's
why we're creating the one that's kind
of owned by humanity
yeah but there are ones like the holo
chain and stuff that again they're not
like who owns it who's actually in
charge of this but the idea is it's
decentralized and you can add on to it I
don't even understand it necessarily but
business structure like how what is the
business structure of it what is the
corporate structure of it how do they
make their money and that's not an easy
column right what is there like this is
unclear so they clearly make their money
from somewhere is a very important piece
Wikipedia is like they make them from
donations right then a lot of Em's ad
revenue or whatever it happens to be
like what are the important pieces cuz
we don't need to fill them all out right
if I hear of next door I can just put
that in put a URL to it and someone else
could fill that out eventually but we
want to be able to have columns for the
things that we care about so that if
they're part of it that would be
especially for people who have projects
in game B right who like Jonelle who has
I can never remember the name of it her
plat for that she's creating that yeah
I'm not gonna it is but she's constantly
adding things to it and having it be
like what's your tagline
what's your elevator pitch she or
Janelle you're the one you know I mean
who's kind of in charge of it and what
is it hope to accomplish and what like
there's ones that will be able to fill
out better because we know the people
creating them and then ones that we
don't but that's part of the lack of
transparency in there in the tech space
and online of how do you trust who's
making it how'd people trust your notes
and they don't know her right yeah like
we'll want to fly and say these are
these are tools from within the
community itself well within the game be
community or the idea cafe community or
yeah
you can do because part of what I would
love to do with them one of our projects
at one point in time is those Maps of
like who owns what right like how much
food is Nestle owned how many companies
is Nestle owned I think it's important
to have that internally as well like
transparently so everyone can see it but
like hey how we know each other's from
the game bSpace right how someone else
might come on board is I don't know I
met them at my kids school right like to
be able to see a how do these people
actually come on board and be part of it
more so with like my brother we meet
tomorrow we're siblings like you know
we've known each other our whole lives
that's an important piece if we're not
putting our last names on the bottom
right like yeah both this dynamic is a
sibling dynamic and also like of a third
persons coming on board and also people
just understand that that I'm going to
trust him more than I'm gonna trust some
other random person that I'm probably
gonna support his ideas and tear them
apart
that's what siblings are for yeah so
that's all I was thinking of columns was
what you know something to kind of say
are these just tools were using or which
might be in the in that category like
you said oh must be the connection
problem that's never happened on here
before oh did I lose you for a minute
yeah yeah we both went there was like
little a little spinning thing on there
and say like if Elon Musk's cuz these
who comes to mind
everyone kind of who has so maybe we
don't need it on him but anyone else who
creates something what were your
previous projects right like stuff that
tracks the person but now I'm getting on
to a whole new project that we're not
doing so I don't know what I'm let's
just jump and create that but like those
are pieces of it right if we know that
these five people are founding members
and they happen to have also been
founding members on these other ones I
think that's like just a part of the
column be able to find people but it's
hard to do on a spreadsheet I think yeah
so I'm wondering like a column just to
indicate whether or not they're from
this these communities and then maybe
one for you know are they
yeah and then like you know what what's
there this is it you know like you have
for profit is one of the things and for
profit not-for-profit cooperative I
don't know
HM blockchain which even blockchain can
be any of those other three like
blockchain has to kind of be there's
like a legal corporate structure what is
it but I don't know how to find that out
for a website but it exists like it's
somewhere online and that's part of
making information that's already exists
and is out there but usable right
creating and the spread she doesn't need
to do all of that but to be able to have
that call and just even own that like
this is a piece of information that
would be great to have even if we don't
have it we might have it for one in ten
of them or one in a hundred of them but
we decide on do we decide on columns
like well we definitely add a category
column
okay so category name which can have the
URL right there it's just easier and
that's also what I did I don't know on
which one oh and the pricing structure
because there's pricing which i think is
an important feature but you can't
really include that in the spreadsheet
so just linking to it back to their
their pricing on theirs right or free
because that's a really easy pricing
structure to put on there right like
Wikipedia is free you don't need to pay
for it and those are important factors I
think I just put like I don't know which
one it was for but I put free - like 60
bucks a month per user and that's what
it is but then I linked back to the to
the pricing structure it was pricing
pricing but I also feel like beyond just
the pricing model like they they're a
subscription base that they charge
monthly that like there's to me at least
as a consumer a big difference between I
have to spend 50 bucks on this software
and then I own it I get to use it
forever versus a monthly fee versus it's
free or I have to see advertisements
right like what is that the word for it
funding model yeah yeah I think funding
model would be good that's like how they
make money so they stay open but there's
also like what it so pricing is what it
cost me funny models how they stay open
yeah category the name you said a
separate one for if it's like people we
know in the game be space or not
necessarily no but yeah people and
people in these spaces you know game be
an idea cafe I don't know contact person
like or people I don't I don't know what
that I mean you had when people call
them there and a second maybe that's it
if we're listing individual people but I
don't know we could put a long must for
SpaceX so that's not the same thing yeah
yeah I mean I don't know we could I
think we could just have like a you know
hmm
I mean maybe we could just put a
community column and so that if the
creator's are owners of it are paro of
one of these communities we could write
down what community they're in so game
be we could put idea cafe to the
together tech yeah no that's okay I
think that's important and like there's
that weird like we're in game be we've
chosen to opt into being game be certain
people like Ken Wilber and I can't think
of anyone else haven't chosen to be in
game be but they've been labeled this
game be those are different things to me
like they haven't labeled themselves
game be they're just like they think
that intake girl falls under a game feed
type space but I think that that's still
I don't know I don't know how to word
that though like almost self defined
community like what if they say they're
part of and then how does that break
down like someone's part of like elf
rally point alpha or whatever it's
called
they're also game be how many what game
be community are they part of the
Twitter one the whatsapp one the discord
like which which one are they actually
are they on all of those well I guess
it's more just what what there
maybe what their philosophy is I think
that is an important part is so that's
like the name the category like their
elevator pitch what's their purpose and
maybe a Czech bar checkmark or something
next to it like directly from them like
there though you don't I mean like if we
know them we know it like this is what
how they've worded the purpose it's very
different than me going and seeing what
you on musk said in an interview but I
don't know how to like categorize that
completely nestos helping here Maidan
references you know that sirs friend who
scenes Oh scenes like the what scene
they're part of its kind of like
community yeah then it could be like
that one's almost like its own with
checkmarks like are they game be are
they Integra I don't know like different
are they also whole out chain there's
people on hollow chain that are blogged
the game be they'd have no those
checkmarks thanks but yeah we've donated
this is even our project yet but like
it's just important to have that like
right I mean maybe even just maybe if
it's just checkbox to say that they're a
member of one of these communities as
opposed to Twitter right yeah so is it
is it a is it a community thing one of
the these broad communities working them
make the world a better place or is it
just some software we found on the
Internet yeah maybe um like instead of
just the contact person of the person
who we could contact Elon Musk to find
out about Tesla like in the transition
org which is a community-based website
for people wanting to transition to a
resource-based economy and I know Nicole
because through Facebook and through
contact me through that she's not part
of game B but like I'm kind of her
contact person right so like who in our
group knows them and it's the contact
person if that makes sense
like who's and other people might also
be like I also know Nicole they're also
a contact person right like that um who
knows them has had a conversation with
them
like who's the warmest contact to
contact them in if that makes sense like
you can even say warm or yeah from our
internal group right like how many
degrees of separation we know these
people just degrees of separation it's
like Jordans had a called I've had a
conversation with Jordan Jordan said a
conversation with them that's two
degrees of separation we're good we're
good yeah
category tech share different scenes yes
but I wouldn't know how to do that
Ernesto seen sort of me space automation
it what we're specifically referring to
are all they would all be tech based I
know I said Tesla but that just comes
out somewhat I know you love mollusk I
know he also has apps and other stuff I
just don't know what they are but these
are all about apps websites technology
specifically because that's what people
keep saying hey have you heard of this
this already exists and then there's
nowhere to put it besides in my head
where it's gonna go out because it's my
because of my memory so yeah as category
references yeah those are important but
also I don't know how to I don't have
the ability to do that on a spreadsheet
yeah I don't know if we want to spend
that much time maintaining that level
detail no it's just it this is why we're
probably ready you know take it too much
time talking about it but having the
bare minimum of columns that like we can
kind of fill out as we find one as we
meet people who are part of their own
tech like even if they're coming on
board to be part of this and they also
have their own technology it's an
important piece to know about right that
yeah is that conflict of interest and
not a conflict of interest it's like hey
yeah I think maybe just a box that
describes maybe even just relation ship
to this idea and then you know we could
just ride out there hey you know these
people were inspired by this idea and
you know for now let it be a paragraph
and then we can and we see a pattern we
can put ten columns sounds good so
anything else you want
talk about today right now before else
need to write down what it is we know
we're gonna brainstorm the missions team
we kind of already came up with the
mission statement but sitting with it
that may be seen whether that
encompasses like you had talked about an
intimate conversation right um yeah and
just think about it a bit and then maybe
we could finalize on next meeting unless
we don't feel comfortable with that yeah
and then the schedule requirements I
think just individually brainstorming
what we think that could look like and
then coming back together and seeing how
much we had in common as well as there's
gonna be ones that you're I'm like yes
we need that and vice versa
yeah yeah great to do together on air so
people can see the discussion yeah
absolutely
right out scheduled requirements and
we've done a bit of that this week but
for me I want to sit down with a piece
of paper and be like as a user here's
what I want it to look like because
that's what I had to offer as far as
I've no idea how to actually code it or
schedule it but like I have scheduled
idea cafes and so I know what work is
involved in that and knowing I don't
even know how to separate those in my
mind like my experience as a user who
wouldn't have anything to do with it and
my experience is the person coordinating
it so I'm gonna sit down and tease those
apart a little bit of legs right those
are very different but important
important features yeah all right so
that is what I'm gonna do between now
and next week next the other question
was just what I had we discussed at the
beginning for if you want to talk about
create like an idea cafe I don't know if
I want a game B idea cafe that's
scheduled the same time every week
because then I know it's in my schedule
and I just want to have those
conversations with game B people then
people know to kind of show up that they
know it's at that that time every time
yeah I don't know if you want to work on
that with me as far as I pick a time
that you know you're generally available
again you don't need to be available
every week that you can come and
participate but both a time it might
work for you that it's not a time you're
definitely not available
yeah and a topic and I'm doing that with
with someone from game B as well she's
the one who had wasn't able to go decks
last week but
being of conflict in the game be space
that coordinating what am a topic
wouldn't look like and that doesn't need
to be one time slot will coordinate with
a time slot that works for her and I and
then put it out to the game be community
who else wants to join the one I'm
talking about I want to have a time
period that works for more people and so
maybe what am I asking a doodle poll so
we can pick times that we're both
usually available and then also putting
a note to them like if we can pick three
or four times and then put it out to the
game be space to see which times more
people because if there's like twelve
people that are available
who will consistently have four people
show up to those ones to be part of it
so yeah I can create a quick doodle poll
and then send you the link and then we
can just I'm my schedule is pretty darn
flexible actually but it may be easier
to kind of coordinate with that I'll
just need to tell everyone you know your
scheduling on this one specific week but
think about all your weeks because they
don't have a thing that says what am I
generally available yes so guess what
I'm asking is I don't want just a doodle
poll minute to go out there and me not
to be available it's a hosted so you and
I need to pick a few times to coordinate
to put on the doodle poll to ask that
gave me people yeah right or me in the
same time zone no with the central
central we're an hour apart yeah what
time is it there right now 1 p.m. 5
205's over 2 hours apart of course it
depends on there are daylight savings
sort of synched up did you have you had
time change or we just at our time
chains we did - we're seeing toughest
countries now yeah that is all right so
yeah that's just part so if you give me
your time that you're available I can
subtract two hours and have it in mind I
just need to know whose time Somer come
in so that that that works yeah it's a
big piece of the scheduler time zones is
like 90% of it yeah right
I I am pretty darn flexible so Sunday
mornings are out or not possible but
most any other time
if I don't have a recurring meeting like
I'm busy at 11 o'clock everyday but
everything else is pretty flexible do
you have any preferred times for me the
best time is when my child is in school
and my brain works better in them or
like before she wakes up so like 6:00
a.m. my time works well however then
sometimes she wakes up during that time
and if we're doing it for her
it's an idea Cafe is half an hour so 6
o'clock in the morning on a weekday
works great the weekends don't work
great I already have my 9:00 a.m. on
Saturdays with my brother and having
other people and I'm trying to keep my
weekends with my kid and you know family
but this is a big priority as far as her
future and the planet so like if other
people are available on Saturdays let's
say 10:00 a.m. I'm down with that
because then at least it's like just
Saturday mornings that I'm concentrating
this and then Saturday afternoons and
all day sunday and Friday afternoons I
have with her
but generally 9:30 in the morning so I
can drop her off at school and walk back
to about 245 s have to be done by 2:45
to go and pick her up
so in in that time period is so I think
if we put that in then I could block out
the times I'm not available it's just
like you said 9:30 was that mine sorry
was that my time 7 years that was that
was mine so that would be 11:30 your
time zone to around 4:45 your time zone
yeah so I don't think I have anything
regularly scheduled in those days of the
week for that all right so do you want
to do just every weekday from 9:30 your
time to highlight 2:45 my time so like
it needs to be done by 2:45 so you'd
want to start - - is the latest we'd
want to start my time from 9:30 to
okay that's just a lot of which is what
I kind of did when I put out the other
one is I was like I kind of had
different days of the week in different
times but I put it about four options
then everyone was available 1:00 p.m. on
Thursday so I put out a bunch of 1:00
p.m. ones and then no one signed up for
them almost like wait was it Thursday
you're obvious was the Thursday really
available for I don't know and this is
part of the scheduler issue and like
doodle polls is great a great tool but
it doesn't really solve this problem for
everyone right or like how do you find
people and bring them together for a
time and be like well I'm available
during these times and like how is there
not a tool out there where I can put in
my schedule you can put in yours and
someone else can in it kind of took them
that I'm surprised
we're in 2019 and doodle finally came
out with those features it's like this
has been something that's been needed
forever I keep thinking I'm gonna build
it but I have other priorities but yeah
this yeah yeah so I'm really I'm
surprised how far we are with calendars
the mere fact that I can't share my
calendar with other people real easily
is just technology it should be it
should be easy for anyone to look up
when I'm available yeah or a group and
you should be able to pick like two or
three people and then just it would tell
you when our calendars are available
that's exactly what we want to happen
are see if we could include that at our
schedule and people are coming on board
just to do that find a time when we can
all meet for a conversation too we want
to be part of that's not the really the
idea cafe but if it was a heart thing we
could make in there so that you know
we've gained be people we want to
discuss this question it's like there's
a group of people who are available all
over the world at their own time periods
put in your time period and we'll find
you people to talk to about this topic
that you care about is huge and then sit
you at a table so you pick a question we
generated some for you yeah want me to
go ahead and make a doodle for that yeah
that'd be great okay all right and then
we can then we're resetting it out to
game B so we're just gonna make pickle
like times in that period you're
available I'm available and then send it
out to game B to see if there and
Twitter like I mean
Facebook Twitter yeah I mean however if
I shoot you the link I think you have
more visibility and can be in stuff
maybe you can post it yeah sounds good
to say it that will have a weekly one
and then um maybe what part of what we
can do is have not a idea cafe but a
zoom conversation on how as an idea as a
game be space we want those to work like
we've picked a time
this is picking the time it's gonna
happen every week and then saying like
do we want to host them and zoom write
it so that it's a breakout groups so
it's bigger do we want to what how do we
want to be able to pick and vote on
questions and that's kind of talking
about those other tools that we've have
use and using them or we just do that
and tell them this is this is the tools
were using and tell us if there's a
better one might be a better option yeah
that might be a little simpler mm-hmm
all right good well I can do that I
think we're over our time we aren't over
our time just ever really a huge issue
but when other people are invited for
like from this time this time if we're
always going over it can be a little a
little not so great but I like this I
like that I'm really grateful that
you're part of this and that we're we're
meeting weekly because I was just I just
went through categorize my my youtube
channel I made like categories and one
thing was like fix the world Fridays and
I have like 6 or 7 weeks of me just
sitting there being like yeah magic
people's questions there's no one here
this is great Mike yet but then you
showed up and I I love it it's great
we're doing this there'll be more people
coming on board and Ernesto has been
here two weeks in a row and that's
appreciated to Ernesto having people pop
in and participated it and put out the
word tell people could find it yeah all
right well thank you Bentley and I will
do the agenda and I'll talk to you next
Friday yep see you there all right take
care
you